Warren S. McCulloch Papers 1860s-1987 Mss.B.M139
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1931-1968; 13.5 lin. feet (Box 1-28)
  - Deutsch, Albert, 1948-1959; 3 items
  - Dewan, Edmond M., 1967; 2 items
  - Diamond, Marian C., 1967; 2 items
  - Diaz, Roberto Moreno, 1965-1968; 7 items
  - Dill, John M., 1959; 2 items
  - Dille, J. M., 1954; 1 item
  - Discovery, 1962; 3 items
  - Ditchburn, R. W., 1959-1960; 3 items
  - Dix, Lester, 1959; 3 items
  - Dixon, Elizabeth, n.d.; 1 item
  - Dixon, John, 1961-1967; 17 items
  - Dixon, Robert E., 1965-1967; 8 items
  - Doehlert, David H., 1958; 4 items
  - Dohrn, Peter, 1964-1967; 13 items
  - Dolphin, Vernon, 1959-1960; 5 items
  - Dondey, Max, 1961-1964
  - Dorny, C. Nelson, 1969; 5 items
  - Doty, Robert W., 1946-1961; 23 items
  - Douglass, E., 1952; 2 items
  - Douglass, E. Van, 1968-1969; 36 items
  - Dounce, Alexander L., 1952-1968; 40 items
  - Dow, Robert S., 1950; 1 item
  - Dragstedt, L. R., 1950; 10 items
  - Draper, J., 1955; 3 items
  - Drever, James, 1954; 1 item
  - Driscoll, Leo, 1963; 1 item
  - Droogleever, Fortuyn, Jan, 1947-1969; 21 item
  - Du Bin, Alexander, 1947; 1 item
  - Du Brul, E. Lloyd, 1959-1967; 16 items
  - Du Brul, E. Lloyd. Biomechanics of the Body, 1963; 2 items
  - Du Brul, Florence Kirsch, 1963-1967; 39 items
  - Ducasse, Pierre, 1952; 1 item
  - Dudley, B., 1957; 1 item
  - Dugger, Elizabeth, 1955; 1 item
  - Duncan, 1952; 4 items
  - Duncan, George Balog, 1948-1982; 6 items
  - Dunn, Joe, 1954; 1 item
  - Dusser De Barenne, Dorothea, 1940-1943; 14 items
  - Dusser De Barenne,. G., 1938-1941
  - Dysinger, Robert H., 1947; 2 items
  - Earle and Reilly., 1945; 1 item
  - The Eastern States Optometric Congress, 1956; 1 item
  - Ebner, Ford F., 1962; 3 items
  - Eccles, J. C., 1947-1948; 4 items
  - Eckstein, Gustav, 1950; 2 items
  - Edin Electronics Company, 1950; 1 item
  - Edwards, Gary I., 1960; 1 item
  - Eisenberg, Leon, 1939-1950; 4 items
  - Elder, James H., 1950; 2 items
  - Electronics, 1965; 2 items
  - Electroshock Research Association, 1949-1950; 2 items
  - Elias, Peter, 1951; 5 items
  - Elkes, Joel, 1953-1956; 4 items
  - Ellerbroek, Wallace C., 1969; 1 item
  - Elliott, K. A. C., 1940; 2 items
  - Ellis, Norman R., 1963; 2 items
  - Emanuel, Alfred, 1945; 2 items
  - Emerson, Robert C., 1966; 2 items
  - Emmi, A. J., 1934; 1 item
  - The Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1946-1958; 20 items
  - Encyclopedia of Library and Information Science, 1966; 3 items
  - Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1961; 3 items
  - Endres, Richard O., 1956-1957; 7 items
  - Enfield College of Technology, 1965-1968; 2 items
  - Engel, Joe, 1969; 1 item
  - England, Samuel .J M., 1967-1968; 11 item
  - Englander, Charles, 1956; 1 item
  - Enroth, Christina, 1959; 1 item
  - Epstein, Sheldon L., 1968; 2 items
  - Erickson, Erick, 1960; 1 item
  - Erickson, T. C., 1945-1952; 4 items
  - Ershov, A. P., 1958; 1 item
  - Escavaille, Betty, 1949-1950; 3 items
  - Esser, Aristide Henri, 1966; 11 item
  - Essig, Carl F., 1948; 2 items
  - Evans, Frank A., 1949; 1 item
  - Evans, Joseph P., 1948-1959; 10 items
  - Everett, G. M., 1960; 1 item
  - Ewald, A. Timothy, 1952; 1 item
  - Exceptional Children, 1952; 1 item
  - Excerpta Medica, 1951; 1 item
  - Experimental Medicine and Surgery, 1945; 2 items
  - Fabing, Howard D., 1953; 4 items
  - Fair, Charles M., 1961; 28 items
  - Falchuk, Kenneth R., 1967; 8 items
  - Fallex, Jean, 1958; 1 item
  - Famiglietti, Ted, 1968; 1 item
  - Fantel, Alan George, 1965; 4 items
  - Fantel, Mrs. Alan George, 1965-1967; 3 items
  - Farhi, Leon E., 1969; 1 item
  - Farnsworth, Dana L., 1953; 1 item
  - Fazio, Cornelio, 1950; 16 items
  - Feder, Herbert, 1964; 1 item
  - Fegersten, Letten, 1960; 1 item
  - Feigl, Herbert, 1955; 1 item
  - Feinberg, I. Michael, 1954-1968; 7 items
  - Feinberg, Louis, 1951; 2 items
  - Feldstein, Leonard C., 1951; 2 items
  - Felix, R. H., 1953-1954; 3 items
  - Fender, Derek H., 1953; 1 item
  - Feng, T. P., 1949; 1 item
  - Fentem, P. H., 1955; 1 item
  - Fernandez, Jose Maria Gonzalez, 1951; 2 items
  - Ferrari, G. Franco, 1966; 1 item
  - Ferry, John D., 1949; 3 items
  - Fessard, A., 1959; 1 item
  - Field, Roger K., 1968; 5 items
  - Fields, William H, Jr., 1951; 2 items
  - Fields, William S., 1950-1962; 2 items
  - Figar, Stepan, 1961; 1 item
  - Finch, Henry A., 1961; 2 items
  - Fincher, Edgar F., 1949-1950; 4 items
  - Finlay, Iseult, 1946-1951; 5 items
  - Fisch, Max H., 1961; 2 items
  - Fischer, Roland, 1962-1969; 10 items
  - Fischgold, H., 1949-1951; 5 items
  - Fisher, Virginia H., 1950; 3 items
  - FitzHugh, Richard, 1962; 2 items
  - Flanigan, Stevenson, 1963; 2 items
  - Flesher, Gail T., 1960; 1 item
  - Flinn, Don, 1961; 1 item
  - Flood, Merrill M., 1952; 2 items
  - Flores, I., 1959-1960; 2 items
  - Flory, L. E., 1949; 2 items
  - Foa, Piero P., 1949; 2 items
  - Fogel, Lawrence J., 1954; 107 items
  - Foley, Edmund, 1941; 2 items
  - Follett, Thomas L., 1964; 4 items
  - Fonda, Albert G., 1948; 3 items
  - Fonseca, Joao L. Simoes da, 1966; 35 items
  - Ford, John J., 1967; 1 item
  - Forster, Francis M., 1948-1949; 4 items
  - Fort Wayne (Ind.) Engineers Club, 1950; 7 items
  - Fortune, 1953-1963; 4 items
  - Foster, A. A., 1963; 2 items
  - Foster, Dean, 1963; 2 items
  - Foster, Robert, 1963; 3 items
  - Francesco, Lauria, 1969; 3 items
  - Francesco, Margaret, 1945; 3 items
  - Franco, George A., 1960-1961; 8 items
  - Frank, Karl, 1961; 3 items
  - Frank, L. K., 1949; 1 item
  - Frank, Philipp G., 1953; 2 items
  - Frank, Richard van, 1961; 1 item
  - Frank, Travel Service, 1953; 2 items
  - Freedman, Burrill, 1950-1962; 54 items
  - Freedman, Nelson L., 1965; 2 items
  - Freedman, Sanford J., 1961-1962; 7 items
  - Freeman, L. W., 1949; 2 items
  - Freeman, R. G., 1950; 3 items
  - Fremont-Smith, Frank, 1942-1950; 112 items
  - Freygang, Walter H., Jr., 1951; 2 items
  - Frick, Frederick C., 1951; 1 item
  - Friedenberg, Robert M., 1955-1969; 13 items
  - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1947; 2 items
  - Friel, Edward, 1968; 1 item
  - Froehlich, Alfred, 1943; 2 items
  - Fromer, Irving R., 1947; 2 items
  - Frontera, José Guillermo, 1959; 2 items
  - Frontiers of Science Foundation, 1956; 1 item
  - Frosst, Charles E. and Co., 1950; 1 item
  - Fruth, Hal F., 1947; 1 item
  - Fry, Glenn, 1961; 2 items
  - Fry, William J., 1949-1969; 37 items
  - Fubini, Eugene G., 1968-1969; 7 items
  - Fujimori, Bunichi, 1959; 2 items
  - Fullington, Gilbert, 1962; 2 items
  - Fulton, John F., 1940-1957; 158 items
  - Furtado, Diogo, 1951; 2 items
  - Gabor, Dennis, 1953-1969; 14 items
  - Gamble, John G., 1961-1963; 6 items
  - Gammon, George D., 1951; 1 item
  - Gannett, E. K., 1958; 1 item
  - Gannon, Robert C., 1959; 1 item
  - Gantt, W. Horsley, 1947-1968; 18 items
  - Garceau, Mrs. Grenville G., 1949; 2 items
  - Gardner, L. B., 1931; 1 item
  - Gardner, Robert D., 1962; 2 items
  - Garian, Robert, 1968-1969; 3 items
  - Garland, Barbara, 1953; 3 items
  - Garol, Hugh W., 1938-1952; 104 items
  - Garven, H. S. D., 1951; 10 items
  - Garvin, John Samuel, 1951; 2 items
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1941-1950; 5 items
  - Gastaut, Henri, 1949-4951; 13 items
  - Gaudfernau, J., 1960; 2 items
  - Gayle, David D., 1968; 9 items
  - Gayral, Louis, 1951; 2 items
  - Gaze, R. M., 1958; 2 items
  - Geiger, Leslie E., 1938; 1 item
  - Geiger, Sara G., 1947; 2 items
  - Geigy Pharmaceuticals, 1958-1959; 2 items
  - Geiser, K. R., 1959; 5 items
  - Gellhorn, Ernest, 1942-1949; 8 items
  - General Electric Co., 1949-1961; 8 items
  - General Foods Corporation, 1956; 1 item
  - General Precision, Inc. Link Division, 1961; 1 item
  - Gentry, Dean, 1947; 2 items
  - Gerard, R. W., 1941-1963; 21 items
  - Gerr, Karl, 1960; 2 items
  - Gerr, Stanley, 1946-1950; 7 items
  - Gerty, Francis J., 1941-1963; 68 items
  - Geschwind, Norman, 1941-1967; 121 items
  - Gesell, Arnold, 1946; 1 item
  - Gesteland, Robert C., 1964-1966; 12 items
  - Giacoletto, L. J., 1958; 2 items
  - Gibbs, Frederic A., 1944-1952; 4 items
  - Gibson, William C., 1952; 10 items
  - Gilbert, Allyn E., 1949; 4 items
  - Gilstrap, Lewey O. Jr., 1965-1968; 12 items
  - Ginsberg, S. T., 1954; 2 items
  - Gitlin, David, 1953-1954; 3 items
  - Glaser, Gilbert H., 1957-1961; 3 items
  - Glees, Paul, 1942-1943; 28 items
  - Glickman, Nathaniel, 1953; 1 item
  - Glickstein, Mitchell, 1960; 1 item
  - Glover, William R., 1961-1962; 3 items
  - Goldman, D. E., 1948; 1 item
  - Goldstein, Gordon, 1960; 1 item
  - Golla, Yolande M. L., 1956-1958; 3 items
  - Gomes, Alair O., 1968; 2 items
  - Gonseth, F., 1956; 1 item
  - Good, I. J., 1960; 2 items
  - Goodall, Marcus, 1955-1969; 18 items
  - Goodenough, John B., 1955; 1 item
  - Goodwin, Brian C., 1964-1969; 3 items
  - Goodwin, Craig, 1951; 4 items
  - Gorosch, Max, 1954; 5 items
  - Gose, Earl Eugene, 1963-1968; 16 items
  - Goshorn, Roy W., 1954-1969; 17 items
  - Gould, Albert E., 1962; 2 items
  - Gozzano, Mario, 1967; 1 item
  - Grader, Frances, 1965; 1 item
  - Graf, Carl J., 1947; 4 items
  - Granit, Ragnar, 1951-1955; 4 items
  - Grant, Ronald, 1948; 2 items
  - Grass, Albert M., 1954; 1 item
  - Grass Instrument Co., 1949; 2 items
  - Gravalos, F. G., 1965; 1 item
  - Graves, Robert W., 1950; 3 items
  - Graves, William A., 1968; 2 items
  - Gray, George W., 1949; 11 item
  - Gray, Harry J., Jr., 1958-1959; 3 items
  - Great Britain. Embassy (U.S.), 1962-1965; 6 items
  - Green, John R., 1959-1965; 12 items
  - Greenblatt, Milton, 1960; 1 item
  - Greene, Charlotte Dusser de Barenne, 1940-1950; 19 items
  - Greene, George, 1949; 1 item
  - Greene, Peter H., 1959-1969; 12 items
  - Greenhill, Maurice H., 1955; 1 item
  - Gregg, Alan, 1946-1949; 3 items
  - Gregory, C., 1961; 1 item
  - Gregory, Richard L., 1956-1969; 6 items
  - Grenell, Robert G., 1947-1948; 2 items
  - Griffith, Coleman R., 1951; 3 items
  - Griffith, John, 1958; 1 item
  - Grollman, Arthur, 1954-1955; 9 items
  - Grose, V. L., 1958-1963; 6 items
  - Gross, Llewellyn, 1956; 1 item
  - Gross, Ronald L., 1957; 1 item
  - Grossman, Charles, 1954-1956; 4 items
  - Groves, W. E., 1963; 4 items
  - Grünbaum, Adolf, 1961; 2 items
  - Grunfest, Harry, 1951-1964; 5 items
  - Gualtierotti, T., 1953; 1 item
  - Guelton, V., 1959; 1 item
  - Guerrant, John S., 1955; 1 item
  - Gunter, Ralph, 1960-1965; 5 items
  - Gunther, Gotthard, 1960-1966; 34 items
  - Guth, Sylvester K., 1954-1956; 6 items
  - Gutiérrez-Mahoney, W. de, 1940-1942; 3 items
  - Gutmann, James, 1955-1956; 5 items
  - Gwin, Cecil, 1965; 1 item
  - Gyarfas, Kalman, 1952; 6 items
  - Haas, Richard A., 1968; 2 items
  - Hack, Marvin Howard, 1949-1951; 12 items
  - Hagedorn, H. C., 1947; 1 item
  - Hague, Eliott B., 1963; 2 items
  - Hakim, Salomón, 1949; 3 items
  - Hakozaki, Soichi, 1962; 4 items
  - Haldane, J. B. S., 1947-1962; 8 items
  - Hall, Gordon L., 1960; 2 items
  - Halpern, George, 1950-1954; 7 items
  - Halstead, Ward Campbell, 1947-1969; 12 items
  - Hamilton, Anne S., 1966; 1 item
  - Hamilton, Charles, n.d.; 1 item
  - Hamilton, Max, 1961; 1 item
  - Hammer, Preston C., 1965; 1 item
  - Hare, J. D., 1961; 4 items
  - Hare, Kendrick, 1 item
  - Harman, Pickney J., 1949-1951; 6 items
  - Harmon, Darell Boyd, Jr., 1952-1958; 8 items
  - Harmon, Leon D., 1960-1962; 6 items
  - Harper and Brothers, 1954-1955; 3 items
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, 1967; 1 item
  - Harrower, Molly, 1948-1965; 17 items
  - Harrowes, William McConnachie, 1949-1969; 61 item
  - Hartford (Conn.) Inter-College Forum, 1957; 1 item
  - Hartgering, James B., 1960-1963; 5 items
  - Harth, Erich, n.d.; 1 item
  - Hartman, Carl G., n.d.; 1 item
  - Hartman, Hyman, 1963-1967; 6 items
  - Harvard University, 1950-1966; 9 items
  - Hasbrouck, Cecil F., 1947; 3 items
  - Haterius, Hans O., 1947; 2 items
  - Hauk, Donald, 1950; 2 items
  - Haverford College Alumni Association, 1949-1969; 7 items
  - Hawkins, David, 1965; 2 items
  - Hawkins, Joseph k, 1957-1959; 5 items
  - Haworth, Lester C., 1949; 1 item
  - Haymaker, Webb, 1947-1969; 13 items
  - Haynes, Walter G., 1945-1946; 2 items
  - Hazen, H. L., n.d.; 1 item
  - Heimburger, Robert F., 1949; 2 items
  - Heinbecker, Peter, 1946; 2 items
  - Heineck, Arthur W., 1961; 1 item
  - Heisler, Friedy B., 1951; 2 items
  - Hellegass, Clarence A., 1952; 3 items
  - Heller, Dean G., 1963; 3 items
  - Helvey, T. C., 1964-1968; 4 items
  - Henneman, Elwood, 1947-1953; 9 items
  - Henri Wild Instruments, 1952; 2 items
  - Henry, Charles E., 1950-1963; 23 items
  - Henry, John P., 1968; 10 items
  - Henshaw, Paul S., 1963-1966; 11 item
  - Herman, Kate, 1957; 2 items
  - Hermann, Howard T., 1949-1950; 17 items
  - Herold, J. Christopher, 1956; 2 items
  - Herrick, C. Judson, 1948-1950; 4 items
  - Herrick, Julia F., 1966; 1 item
  - Herrman, Heinz, 1951; 2 items
  - Herron, R. E., 1967; 2 items
  - Hersey, Francis, 1962; 4 items
  - Hess, Benno, 1966-1967; 3 items
  - Hess, W. R., 1949-1951; 9 items
  - Heyn, A. N. J., 1961; 1 item
  - Heyl, Caro (Mrs. Arthur F), 1955-1960; 4 items
  - Hick, Ford K., 1952; 1 item
  - Hickox, David B., 1956; 1 item
  - Hicks, W. E., 1950; 2 items
  - Hicks, W. Wesley, 1953; 2 items
  - Hilgartner, C. Andrew, 1968; 2 items
  - Hill, Christopher S., 1969; 2 items
  - Hill, Randolph, 1951; 2 items
  - Hiltz, F., 1965-1966; 2 items
  - Himwich, Harold E., 1956-1965; 47 items
  - Himwich, Williamina A., 1968; 1 item
  - Hines, Marion, 1937-1941; 9 items
  - Hitchcock, Dian, 1959-1969; 13 items
  - Hitchcock, Fred A., 1948; 2 items
  - Hletko, Pacircul, 1950; 2 items
  - Hoagland, Hudson, 1948-1961; 43 items
  - Hoar, Horace, 1963; 1 item
  - Hoar, Leonora, 1949; 2 items
  - Hodgkin, A. L., 1950; 5 items
  - Hoerner, Earl F., 1955-1966; 8 items
  - Hoff, Ebbe Curtis, 1966; 1 item
  - Hoffer, A., 1950; 2 items
  - Hoffstadt, Ellsworth E., 1962; 1 item
  - Holden, Alistair, 1962-1966; 9 items
  - Holland, A. L., 1966; 1 item
  - Hollander, Gerhard L., 1965; 1 item
  - Holloway, Frank L., 1950; 2 items
  - Holshauser, Arthur L., 1969; 5 items
  - Holt, J. P., 1947; 1 item
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1968; 4 items
  - Hope, Lawrence F., 1953-1954; 6 items
  - Hopkins, Herbert, 1948; 1 item
  - Horan, J. S., 1950; 2 items
  - Horowitz, Harold, 1958; 1 item
  - Horowitz, Phill, 1960-1964; 4 items
  - Hoskins, Roy, 1953; 3 items
  - Householder, Alston S., 1947-1950; 6 items
  - Houston Speech and Hearing Center, 1962; 2 items
  - Hove, Edwin L., 1959; 2 items
  - Howard, Katherine, 1956; 1 item
  - Howe, Howard A., 1944; 1 item
  - Howe, Wilfred H., 1956; 1 item
  - Howland, Bradford, 1953; 1 item
  - Howland, W. E., 1953; 2 items
  - Hughes, Harold K., 1966-1969; 8 items
  - Hughes Research and Development Labs., 1959; 2 items
  - Hunt, Preston, 1955; 1 item
  - Hunter, Jessamine, 1947; 1 item
  - Huskey, Harry D., 1950; 1 item
  - Hutchinson, Evelyn, 1965; 1 item
  - Hydén, Holger, 1959; 2 items
  - Hyman, Mat, 1962-1966; 2 items
  - Iberall, Arthur S., 1962-1969; 66 items
  - Ignatius, Benjamin Richard, 1949; 2 items
  - Iliff, Helen, 1968; 1 item
  - Illinois. Department of Public Welfare, 1942; 2 items
  - Illinois Association for Applied Psychology, 1947; 4 items
  - Illinois Institute of Technology-Alumni Association, 1951; 5 items
  - Illinois Neuropsychiatric Institute-Joint Committee on Management, 1943; 4 items
  - Illinois Psychiatric Research Council, 1950; 5 items
  - Illinois State Medical Society, 1951; 1 item
  - Illinois State Psychopathic Institute, 1951; 1 item
  - Indiana University. Institute of Psychiatric Research, 1960; 2 items
  - Indiana University Press, 1965-1966; 3 items
  - Ingebritsen, Karl J., 1962-1966; 8 items
  - Ingle, David J., 1962; 2 items
  - Ingraham, R. P., 1953-1954; 9 items
  - Ingvar, David H., 1953; 2 items
  - Innovation (magazine), 1963-1969; 5 items
  - Institute for the Living, 1947-1950; 9 items
  - Institute for the Unity of Science, 1956; 1 item
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1966-1967; 6 items
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc., 1967-1969; 10 items
  - Institute of Medicine of Chicago, 1943-1949; 3 items
  - Institute of Perception, 1966; 2 items
  - Institute of Radio Engineers, 1955-1961; 11 item
  - Institute of Radio Engineers. Chicago, 1950; 3 items
  - International Bluebook, 1950; 5 items
  - Inwood, Eugene R., 1953; 3 items
  - Irtem, Ali, 1960-1962; 3 items
  - Isaacs, Alexander J., 1954-1956; 15 items
  - Isaacs, Jane, 1960-1966; 6 items
  - Iséki, Kiyoshi, 1962; 1 item
  - Isenson, Raymond S., 1963; 2 items
  - Iversen, Olav H., 1964; 1 item
  - Ivy, Andrew C., 1947-1951; 22 items
  - Jacobi, George T., 1959-1963; 5 items
  - Jacobs, Jack, 1961; 1 item
  - Jacobson, Edmund, 1966; 1 item
  - Jacobson, James, 1946-1951; 2 items
  - Jaglowski, Florence, 1952; 1 item
  - Jahrreiss, Walter O., 1954; 1 item
  - Jackson and Moreland, 1969; 2 items
  - James, Brennig, 1968; 1 item
  - Jampolsky, Arthur, 1953-1954; 2 items
  - Janies, Edmund G., 1946-1947; 3 items
  - Jannotta, Frank S., 1952; 2 items
  - Janz, George J., 1953; 2 items
  - Jarrell-Ash Company, 1953; 1 item
  - Jarvaik, Murray E., 1950-1951; 9 items
  - Jarvis, Kenneth W., 1951-1966; 21 item
  - Jaski, Thomas, 1953; 4 items
  - Jasper, Herbert H., 1947-1968; 29 items
  - Jefferson, Geoffrey, 1950-1957; 3 items
  - Jeffress, Lloyd A., 1950; 2 items
  - Jenerick, Howard, 1958; 4 items
  - Jenik, Franz, 1962; 1 item
  - Jenkins, Richard L., 1950; 5 items
  - Johannesma, Peter, 1967; 1 item
  - Johanningsmeir, A., 1962; 2 items
  - John, Erwin Roy, 1951-1957; 10 items
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1941-1963; 30 items
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc., 1941-1961; 60 items
  - Johnson, Avery R., 1964-1967; 10 items
  - Johnson, Ernest, 1952; 2 items
  - Johnson, John I., 1954; 1 item
  - Jokl, Ernst, 1954; 1 item
  - Jonas, F., 1950; 2 items
  - Jonas, Serge, 1949; 1 item
  - Jones, D. J., 1949-1951; 3 items
  - Jones, George Lee, 1951; 1 item
  - Jones, Richard W., 1959; 2 items
  - Jones, Robert G., 1952; 6 items
  - Jong, Russell de, 1949-1950; 3 items
  - Jonkman, E. J., 1967; 1 item
  - Joos, Georg, 1950; 1 item
  - Jordan, William K., 1961; 1 item
  - Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 1950-1951; 4 items
  - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1950-1952; 8 items
  - Journal of Mental Science, 1953; 1 item
  - Journal of Nervous and Mental Diseases, 1962; 2 items
  - Journal of Nervous and Mental Diseases: in re Norbert Wiener Tribute Volume, 1964-1965; 12 items
  - Journal of Neurophysiology, 1950-1956; 17 items
  - Jouvet, Michel, 1967; 4 items
  - Joyner, Lea W., 1967-1968; 4 items
  - Judd, Art, 1968; 1 item
  - Julian, Fred J., 1955; 3 items
  - Jung, R., 1952-1959; 6 items
  - Jurgen, Ronald K., 1968; 2 items
  - Kaada, Birger, 1959; 2 items
  - Kabrinsky, Matthew, 1964-1966; 1 item
  - Kafarian, Haig, 1966-1969; 10 items
  - Kalaba, Robert, 1960; 1 item
  - Kalin, Theodore, 1961; 2 items
  - Kämpfner, Paul, 1963; 1 item
  - Kampmeier, Otto F., 1947-1952; 11 item
  - Kanavy, C. C, 1968; 1 item
  - Kaneff, Stephen, 1961-1962; 4 items
  - Kang, Christopher, 1959; 1 item
  - Karagulla, S., 1952; 1 item
  - Karchmar, E. Jane, 1961; 3 items
  - Karten, David, 1960; 1 item
  - Katz, Arnold, 1966; 2 items
  - Kauffman, Stuart A., 1967-1969; 44 items
  - Keeler, Martin, H., 1962; 1 item
  - Keeton, Robert W., 1947-1949; 9 items
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1948; 2 items
  - Kempinsky, W. H., 1950; 4 items
  - Kendig, M., 1960; 7 items
  - Kennady, John B., 1950-1952; 2 items
  - Kennard, Margaret A., 1947-1954; 18 items
  - Kennedy, Foster, 1948; 1 item
  - Kennedy, John L., 1949-1956; 4 items
  - Kennedy, Ralph C., 1950; 2 items
  - Kennedy, Thelma Temy, 1948-1950; 6 items
  - Kennedy Airport, 1968; 1 item
  - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1961-1968; 8 items
  - Kessler, Laibe A., 1955-1961; 9 items
  - Kessler, William J., 1949; 2 items
  - Kety, Seymour S., 1950-1951; 6 items
  - Khanna, S. M., 1957-1958; 2 items
  - Kidd, Geoffrey, 1956; 1 item
  - Kidwell, Robert P., 1965; 1 item
  - Kiepe, Paul, 1951-1956; 2 items
  - Kiliany, William, 1963; 1 item
  - Kilmer, William L., 1961-1965; 42 items
  - Kirner, Walter R., 1948; 4 items
  - Kissin, Benjamin, 1952; 2 items
  - Kjellberg, Raymond N., 1964; 1 item
  - Klaczko-Ryndizium, Salomon, 1960; 5 items
  - Klein, J. Raymond, 1947; 14 items
  - Klein, Louise H., 1963; 2 items
  - Kline, Mars, 1959; 1 item
  - Kline, Nathan S., 1968-1969; 2 items
  - Klingman, W. O., 1947; 1 item
  - Klock, Peter A., 1965; 4 items
  - Klüver, Heinrich, 1953-1966; 12 items
  - Knight, J. F., 1949; 1 item
  - Knisely, Melvin H., 1952-1958; 6 items
  - Knoll, Max, 1962; 5 items
  - Kobageshi, n.d.; 1 item
  - Kobler, John, 1949; 2 items
  - Koch, General Summary of work... MIT, 1954; 3 items
  - Koch, F. C., 1944; 1 item
  - Kochen, Manfred, 1957; 1 item
  - Kockinos, C. N., 1968-1969; 6 items
  - Koffler, Arthur, 1959; 2 items
  - Koketsu, K., 1952; 1 item
  - Kolowsky, Lynn, 1962-1963; 2 items
  - Konecci, Eugene B., 1966-1967; 5 items
  - Kopeloff, Nicholas, 1947-1948; 7 items
  - Korn, Karl, 1965-1967; 2 items
  - Kornmann, Anton P., n.d.; 2 items
  - Korr, Irwin M., 1949; 1 item
  - Kosik, Jean Claude, 1964; 2 items
  - Koskoff, Yale David, 1952-1969; 59 items
  - Kozmetsky, George, 1968; 1 item
  - Kraines, Samuel Henry, 1945-1955; 12 items
  - Krapf, E. E, 1951; 1 item
  - Kraus, K. J., 1958; 1 item
  - Krause, Gilbert, 1956; 5 items
  - Kreezer, George L., 1947; 2 items
  - Kremer, James N., 1965; 2 items
  - Kremer, John, 1942-1943; 18 items
  - Krenfeld, Peter C., 1961; 1 item
  - Krieg, Wendell J. S., 1953; 5 items
  - Kris, Christine, 1953; 5 items
  - Krohn, Bernard G., 1968-1969; 6 items
  - Kronenberg, Gisela, 1947-1948; 26 items
  - Kruse, H. D., 1950; 5 items
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1943-1968; 17 items
  - Kuffler, Stephen W., 1953-1969; 49 items
  - Kuiper, J. W., 1959-1965; 6 items
  - Kulash, Damien, 1962; 1 item
  - Kun, Ernest, 1949; 1 item
  - Kunov, Hans, 1963; 2 items
  - Kurjian, J. G., 1969; 3 items
  - Kurntz, S., 1952; 2 items
  - Kwee, Him Hok, 1962; 2 items
  - Kyburg, Henry E., Jr., 1961-1968; 21 items
  - Labbé, Paul, 1952; 1 item
  - Lahm, Molly, 1959-1963; 6 items
  - Lampard, Douglas, 1954; 1 item
  - Lamson, Roy, 1961; 3 items
  - Landahl, H. D., 1953-1967; 8 items
  - Landau, Rubin H., 1964-1965; 6 items
  - Landeman, Joy, 1 item
  - Landis, 1949; 1 item
  - Landsberg, P. T., 1963; 1 item
  - Landy, Jerome J., 1950; 3 items
  - Lange, Hendrik de, 1957; 1 item
  - Langley Porter Neuropsychiatric Inst., 1969; 2 items
  - Lanier, Harold H., 1947; 1 item
  - Larrabee, Martin G., 1948; 1 item
  - Lascelle, L. E., 1953; 1 item
  - Lashley, K. S., 1954; 1 item
  - Latil, Pierre de, 1950; 3 items
  - Lauria, F., 1961; 1 item
  - Lawlor, Reed C., 1959; 3 items
  - Lazur, John W., 1959; 1 item
  - Leaké, Chauncey, 1947-1953; 7 items
  - Lechimski, J. M., 1951-1952; 5 items
  - Lederle Laboratories, 1948; 2 items
  - Ledley, Robert S., 1958-1961; 125 items
  - Ledyard W. William, 1947; 2 items
  - Lee, John C., 1959-1963; 4 items
  - Lee, Y. W., 1947; 2 items
  - Lees, Nelson C., n.d.; 1 item
  - Legendy, Charles Rudolf, 1967-1969; 6 items
  - Lehman, A. J., 1949; 4 items
  - Leibovic, K. Nichalas, 1965-1969; 23 items
  - Leigh, Denis, 1948-1949; 2 items
  - Leimdorfer, Alfred, 1951-1954; 9 items
  - Leiner, Henrietta, 1963; 3 items
  - Lendrum, Frederick C., 1948-1953; 21 item
  - Lennox, Margaret A., 1960; 4 items
  - Lettvin, Jerome Y., 1948-1964; 24 items
  - Levenstein, Harold, 1959; 2 items
  - Lever Brothers Company, 1957; 1 item
  - Levin, Louis, 1953; 3 items
  - Levine, Daniel S., 1969; 2 items
  - Levinson Research Foundation, 1952; 2 items
  - Levitt, Morton, 1969; 4 items
  - Levy, Charles K., 1959; 2 items
  - Lewontin, R. C., 1968; 4 items
  - Lhamon, William T., 1949; 3 items